I CANNOT BELIEVE
THAT YOU DIDN'T TELL ME
WE ARE
STILL MARRIED.
LOOK, I WAS GOING TO TELL YOU.
WHEN? AFTER THE BIRTH
OF OUR FIRST SECRET CHILD?
ROSS DIDN'T
GET THE ANNULMENT.
WE ARE STILL MARRIED.
WHAT?
OH, MY GOD!
ROSS?
OKAY, MAYBE IT WASN'T
MY BEST DECISION
BUT I JUST COULDN'T FACE
ANOTHER FAILED MARRIAGE.
LET ME JUST
JUMP IN AND ASK.
AT WHAT POINT
DID YOU THINK
THIS WAS
A SUCCESSFUL MARRIAGE?
RACH, COME ON.
IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
IT'S ACTUALLY KIND OF FUNNY.
MAYBE IT'S BEST
NOT TO THINK ABOUT IT.
THIS IS INEXCUSABLE.
I AM SHOCKED TO MY VERY CORE.
PHOEBE, I TOLD HER
YOU ALREADY KNEW.
ANOTHER LIE.
YOU HAVE A SICKNESS.
ROSS, JUST FOR
MY OWN PEACE OF MIND
YOU'RE NOT MARRIED
TO ANY MORE
OF US, ARE YOU?
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
YO, HEY, SOMEONE
LEFT THEIR KEYS.
OOH! TO A PORSCHE, HUH?
HEY, GUNTHER, THESE YOURS?
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT I DRIVE.
I MAKE FOUR BUCKS AN HOUR.
I SAVED UP FOR 350 YEARS.
AW...
HEY, DID ANYBODY
LOSE THEIR KEYS?
JOEY, WHY DON'T
YOU PUT THEM
IN THE LOST AND FOUND?
THERE'S A LOST AND FOUND?
MY SHOE!
YOU LEFT A SHOE HERE?
WELL, I DIDN'T REALIZE
TILL I GOT HOME.
I WASN'T GOING
TO WALK ALL THE WAY
BACK DOWN HERE WITH ONE SHOE.
I'M GOING TO GO
FIND THAT GUY'S CAR
AND LEAVE A NOTE
ON THE WINDSHIELD.
WHEN HE COMES BACK
FOR HIS KEYS
I'LL BE SURE TO
GIVE HIM YOUR SHOE.
GREAT. THANKS.
OH, GOOD, GOOD.
YOU GUYS ARE HERE.
LISTEN.
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE
TO SPEND TOMORROW
TAKING CARE OF THREE
INCREDIBLY CUTE LITTLE PUPPIES?
MY GOD! WHAT A FUN DAY.
THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
OKAY. WELL, I'LL
BRING THEM BY
TOMORROW MORNING.
OKAY, AND, UM... BY THE WAY,
THEIR NOT ACTUALLY PUPPIES.
THEY'RE FRANK AND ALICE'S
TRIPLETS.
OKAY, SEE YA.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA! WHAT?
PLEASE, PLEASE,
OH, PLEASE.
FRANK AND ALICE
ASKED ME
TO BABY-SIT THE TRIPLETS,
AND I'M NERVOUS.
I'VE NEVER DONE THAT BEFORE
BY MYSELF.
DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT, PHEEB.
WE'LL ABSOLUTELY DO IT.
YEAH,
I'M GOING TO PASS
'CAUSE I WAS KIND OF IFFY
WHEN IT WAS PUPPIES.
COME ON,
CHANDLER, COME ON.
IT WILL GIVE US
GREAT PRACTICE
FOR WHEN PEOPLE
WITH BABIES COME TO VISIT.
NICE CAR.
YEAH. IT'S, UH... IT'S NOT MINE.
I LOVE YOUR CAR.
YEAH. IT'S... MINE.
I'LL BET IT'S FAST.
ME, TOO. YEAH.
AND COMFORTABLE.
DO YOU, UH... DO YOU
LIKE LEATHER SEATS?
YEAH.
IT'S GOT 'EM.
SO, I STILL
HAVE BOXES HERE
I STILL HAVE
BOXES AT ROSS'
AND I HAVE NOWHERE TO LIVE.
WOW, I CAN SO EASILY
FREAK OUT RIGHT NOW.
OKAY, WHAT ABOUT ME?
I JUST FOUND OUT DENISE
IS LEAVING TOWN FOR A WHILE.
I DON'T HAVE A ROOMMATE.
WELL, MAYBE...
MAYBE I CAN
BE YOUR ROOMMATE, PHEEBS.
MAYBE YOU COULD BE MY ROOMMATE.
WELL, THERE'S AN IDEA.
YEAH!
THAT WOULD
BE GREAT!
WAIT. HOW LONG
IS DENISE GONE FOR?
UM... SHE SAID SHE'D
BE BACK DECEMBER 26.
OH, DECEMBER 26.
HA! MAYBE SHE'S SANTA CLAUS.
OH, LOOK WHO IT IS.
MY HUSBAND.
THE APPLE OF MY EYE.
OKAY, I GOT US
A COURT DATE
FOR TOMORROW AT 2:00
AND I PICKED UP ALL THE FORMS.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF EVERYTHING.
WELL, SURE.
IF YOU SAY YOU'RE GOING
TO TAKE CARE OF EVERYTHING
I HAVE NO REASON TO DOUBT YOU.
GIVE ME THOSE FORMS.
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
I'M GOING TO
DO THIS MY WAY
AND I DON'T WANT TO HEAR
A PEEP OUT OF YOU.
OKAY, RACH, BUT...
AH! YOU'RE PEEPING.
( mumbling )
ROSS, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I JUST GOT...
WHY? WHY
DID YOU DO THIS?
LOOK, I TOLD YOU I...
I DON'T WANT
TO HEAR THREE FAILED MARRIAGES.
LOOK, IF YOU'D HAD
TWO FAILED MARRIAGES
YOU'D UNDERSTAND.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT?
THANKS TO YOU
I'M HALFWAY THERE.
OH! OH, I AM
SO MAD, ROSS.
I DON'T THINK
I'VE EVER BEEN THIS ANGRY.
WHAT ABOUT THE TIME
I SAID WE WERE ON A BREAK?
OH!
PHEEB, HOW'S IT GOING?
I'M DOING OKAY.
IT'S GOING WELL.
YOU THINK THEY'RE HAVING FUN?
AM I TALKING TOO FAST?
NO. SOUND LIKE ME.
PHEEBS,
IT'S GOING GREAT.
LOOK AT CHANDLER
WITH LITTLE BABY GIRL CHANDLER.
LITTLE BABY GIRL CHANDLER?
WHERE HAVE I HEARD THAT BEFORE?
OH, RIGHT-- COACH RUBIN.
OOH!
YOU KNOW WHAT, PHEEBS?
WHEN YOU'RE DONE OVER THERE
WE'VE GOT A KIND
OF SITUATION OVER HERE, TOO.
UH-UH. NO.
WE ARE ALL RESPONSIBLE
FOR OUR OWN BABIES.
SEE, THAT'S WHERE
I THINK THAT YOU'RE WRONG.
WE'VE BEEN PLAYING
THESE BABIES MAN-TO-MAN.
WE SHOULD REALLY
BE PLAYING A ZONE DEFENSE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I JUST THINK
THINGS WILL GO A LOT SMOOTHER
IF WE EACH HAVE OUR OWN ZONE.
PHOEBE, YOU CAN
BE IN CHARGE OF WIPING.
AND, YOU KNOW, MON
YOU CAN BE IN CHARGE
OF DIAPERING.
AND I CAN BE IN CHARGE
OF LOOKING HOW CUTE THEY ARE
WHEN THEY PUT
THEIR HANDS AROUND...
THAT SOUNDS REALLY GREAT.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
BE IN CHARGE OF WIPING.
OKAY, I'M A ROOKIE.
I SHOULD NOT BE IN THE END ZONE.
Monica:
THIS IS SO GREAT.
THIS IS EXACTLY HOW WE SET
THE PLATES AT THE RESTAURANT.
OH, YEAH?
WELL,
THIS IS NOT WHAT I ORDERED.
HEY, GUYS.
HI.
HEY.
HEY, BABIES.
OH, I'M HAVING
THE BEST MORNING.
THAT PORSCHE
I'VE GOT THE KEYS TO--
IT'S STILL THERE.
SHOCKING, SINCE YOU
STILL HAVE THE KEYS.
YOU SHOULD SEE THE TREATMENT
I GET WHEN I'M WITH THAT CAR.
PEOPLE ARE FRIENDLY,
THEY WANT TO TALK
AND NOT JUST ABOUT THE CAR.
ONE GUY GAVE ME ADVICE
ABOUT MY EQUITY INVESTMENTS.
WHAT EQUITY INVESTMENTS?
THE ONES THAT
GOT ME THE PORSCHE.
WILL YOU KEEP UP?
BUT I FIGURED IF PEOPLE KEEP
SEEING ME JUST STANDING THERE
THEY'RE GOING TO START
TO THINK I DON'T OWN IT
SO, I FIGURED I'LL WASH IT,
RIGHT?
MONICA, YOU GOT A BUCKET
AND SOME SOAP I CAN BORROW?
OH, YEAH.
I GOT SOAP AND
SPONGES AND RAGS
AND CARNUBA WAX
AND POLISHING COMPOUND.
YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE A CAR.
I KNOW, BUT ONE TIME
THERE WAS THIS REALLY DIRTY CAR
PARKED IN FRONT OF THE BUILDING,
SO I WASHED IT.
AND?
AND SIX OTHERS.
THERE YOU ARE.
YEAH, SHE TOPS OUT AT 130.
WOW.
AND THAT'S JUST
IN THE CITY.
I GET HER UP TO 160
WHEN I TAKE HER UPSTATE.
REALLY?
YOU GOT A PLACE UPSTATE?
SURE.
WELL, I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
OKAY. TAKE IT EASY.
HEY, THAT'S MY CAR.
REALLY? OH. UH...
JUST GIVE ME
FIVE MORE MINUTES, WILL YOU?
WHAT...
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, I...
I FOUND THE KEYS
AND NOW I'M JUST
POLISHING HER UP.
BUT IT'S MY CAR.
YEAH, BUT IT'S MY WAX.
LISTEN, I DON'T COME
TO THE CITY MUCH
AND I DON'T KNOW
IF YOU'RE CRAZY
OR IF THIS IS SOME
KIND OF STREET THEATER...
BUT COULD
I HAVE MY KEYS?
SURE. HERE.
I'LL SAVE YOU A PARKING SPOT.
I'M NOT COMING BACK.
WHY NOT?
I LIVE UPSTATE.
YEAH, SO DID I.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I WAS
SO NERVOUS ABOUT THIS.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHY
FRANK AND ALICE ARE
ALWAYS COMPLAINING.
THIS IS SO EASY.
YEAH, TWO HOURS, A LIFETIME--
THAT'S THE SAME.
CHECK IT OUT. CHECK IT OUT.
WHEN THE BABIES WAKE UP,
THEY CAN MEET KROG.
CHANDLER, WHAT
ARE YOU DOING?
THAT THING COULD PUT
SOMEONE'S EYE OUT.
HE CAN DO MORE THAN THAT.
HE CAN DESTROY THE UNIVERSE.
NO. CHANDLER, THEY COULD SWALLOW
ONE OF THOSE LITTLE PARTS.
AND ALSO, LOOK
AT HIS SMOOTH AREA--
THAT'S JUST GOING
TO MESS THEM UP.
LOOK, THEY'RE NOT GOING
TO SWALLOW ANYTHING.
YOU GUYS ARE BEING
WAY TOO OVERPROTECTIVE.
WHEN I WAS A KID,
MY MOM USED TO JUST THROW ME
INTO A PILE OF BROKEN GLASS.
WHAT?
GLASS, SAND, WHATEVER.
OH, LOOK AT LITTLE LESLIE
STRETCHING IN HER SLEEP.
OH, IT'S SO CUTE.
I WONDER WHAT AGE IT IS
THAT YOU STOP BEING ABLE
TO PUT BOTH LEGS
BEHIND YOUR HEAD?
OH, I CAN STILL DO THAT.
HOW ARE YOU
STILL SINGLE?
ALL RIGHT.
I'VE THOUGHT ABOUT IT
AND MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
MAYBE KROG IS
NOT A SAFE TOY.
GOOD. WHAT CHANGED YOUR MIND?
I SWALLOWED HIS
SONIC BLASTER GUN.
Phoebe:
WHAT?
HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
WELL, I WAS TRYING TO PROVE
THAT I WAS RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, AND
IT TURNS OUT I WAS WRONG
AND... NOW IT'S LODGED
IN MY THROAT.
DAMN IT. YOU KNOW,
THIS WHOLE TIME
WE WERE CONCENTRATING
ON THE BABIES
AND NO ONE WAS WATCHING
CHANDLER.
( gagging )
OKAY, YOU TWO ARE ASKING
THE COURT FOR AN ANNULMENT?
YES, YOUR HONOR
AND HERE ARE OUR FORMS,
ALL FILLED OUT.
SO, BASED ON
YOUR PETITION
YOU ARE SEEKING AN ANNULMENT
ON THE GROUNDS
THAT MR. GELLER
IS MENTALLY UNSTABLE?
FINE. I'M MENTALLY
UNSTABLE.
AND BASED ON THE FACT
THAT MR. GELLER
IS AN INTRAVENOUS DRUG USER?
WHAT?
UH, YES, HEROIN AND CRACK.
CRACK ISN'T EVEN
AN INTRAVENOUS DRUG.
WELL, YOU WOULD KNOW.
NOW, IT ALSO SAYS HERE
THAT YOU, UM
LIED ABOUT YOUR SEXUAL
PREFERENCE BEFORE MARRIAGE.
OH, COME ON.
ROSS, PLEASE.
I FOUND THE MAGAZINES.
AND FINALLY,
THAT YOU WERE UNABLE
TO CONSUMMATE THE MARRIAGE.
WELL, THAT MAKES SENSE
SINCE YOU'RE GAY
AND ADDICTED TO HEROIN.
OKAY, YOU KNOW,
I'M SORRY...
THIS IS INSANE.
I'M NOT ADDICTED TO HEROIN.
I'M NOT GAY
AND THERE IS NO PROBLEM
WITH MY ABILITY
TO CONSUMMATE ANYTHING.
LOOK, I'LL CONSUMMATE THIS
MARRIAGE RIGHT HERE, RIGHT NOW.
THAT WON'T BE NECESSARY.
AND WHEN WE WERE DATING,
WE CONSUMMATED LIKE BUNNIES.
AH!
NOW, IF YOU TWO WERE INVOLVED
IN A SERIOUS RELATIONSHIP
THAT REALLY CREATES A PROBLEM.
YOUR HONOR, REST ASSURED
THAT RELATIONSHIP
ENDED TWO YEARS AGO
AND CAN YOU PLEASE STRIKE
"CONSUMMATED LIKE BUNNIES"
FROM THE RECORD?
IS THERE ANYTHING IN THIS RECORD
THAT IS ACTUALLY TRUE?
WELL, YES, WE GOT MARRIED
IN VEGAS
AND, UH...
THE NAMES, I THINK.
WELL, BASED ON WHAT I'VE HEARD
YOU TWO CERTAINLY DON'T QUALIFY
FOR AN ANNULMENT.
IF YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE TOGETHER
YOU'LL HAVE TO FILE FOR DIVORCE.
THAT'S GREAT.
YOU HAPPY NOW?
LOOK WHAT YOU DID WITH
YOUR FUNNY, FUNNY FORM.
WHAT? ME?
WHAT ABOUT YOU
AND YOUR "CONSUMMATED
LIKE BUNNIES" NONSENSE?
IT WAS...
WHAT ARE YOU
TYPING THAT FOR?
SHE ALREADY SAID
WE DON'T GET THE ANNULMENT.
DON'T TYPE THAT.
STOP TYPING.
HEY. STOP TYPING.
STOP TYPING!
OKAY. OKAY.
DO YOU SEE?
DO YOU SEE WHAT YOU'RE
KEEPING ME MARRIED TO?
YOU NEED TO GET OUT
OF MY CHAMBERS.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK, LADY,
HERE IS THE DEAL:
I CAME HERE
FOR AN ANNULMENT
AND I AM NOT LEAVING HERE
UNTIL I GET ONE.
WANT TO SPEND
THE NIGHT IN JAIL?
OKAY, THANK YOU
FOR YOUR TIME.
( hoarse screech )
( gargles )
SO THAT PORSCHE GUY
TOOK HIS CAR BACK.
BUT YOU FOUND THE KEYS
TO HIS CLOTHES?
NO. I JUST, UH...
I JUST LOVE THE WAY IT FEELS
WHEN EVERYBODY THINKS
I OWN A PORSCHE.
AND PEOPLE WILL THINK
YOU OWN A PORSCHE
BECAUSE YOU'RE
WEARING THE CLOTHES?
OF COURSE.
ONLY AN IDIOT
WOULD WEAR THIS STUFF
IF HE DIDN'T HAVE THE CAR.
THAT IS TRUE.
YEAH, BUT ONLY A GENIUS WOULD
SWALLOW A SONIC BLASTER GUN.
OH, I'VE BEEN THERE.
WELL, I AM GOING TO GO DRIVE
MY PORSCHE.
JOEY, YOU KNOW YOU DON'T
ACTUALLY HAVE ONE.
COME ON.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M IN CHARACTER.
WILL YOU TALK TO HER?
AH, I THINK IT JUST MOVED.
IT'S REALLY POKING ME.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT.
WE'RE GOING
TO THE EMERGENCY ROOM.
WHAT? NO, YOU CAN'T
LEAVE ME HERE WITH THEM.
WE'RE BABY-SITTING.
THE BABIES ARE ASLEEP.
I'M SURE YOU'LL BE
OKAY FOR A WHILE.
BUT YOU CAN'T LEAVE ME
WITH THEM.
WE'RE A TEAM.
WE'RE PLAYING A ZONE.
THEY'RE GOING TO TRIPLE-TEAM ME.
HE'S GOT SOMETHING PLASTIC
LODGED INTO HIS THROAT.
WE'VE GOT TO GO
TO THE HOSPITAL.
BUT, NO, BECAUSE A DOCTOR
WON'T BE ABLE TO HELP HIM.
IT'S JUST GOING TO, YOU KNOW
NATURALLY PASS THROUGH HIS
SYSTEM IN, LIKE, SEVEN YEARS.
I THINK THAT'S GUM.
I'M PRETTY SURE
IT'S GUN.
OKAY, LISTEN, THIS
REALLY HURTS. LET'S GO.
BUT NO, A REAL MAN WOULDN'T
JUST RUN TO THE HOSPITAL.
NO... WHAT WOULD KROG DO?
OH, WHY ISN'T THAT VALET
BACK WITH MY PORSCHE?
MAYBE BECAUSE
YOU'VE GOT THE KEYS.
PORSCHE.
THAT WAS TOTALLY YOUR FAULT.
MY FAULT?
YOU THREATENED THE JUDGE.
WELL, YOU RIPPED
THE PAPER
OUT OF THE COURT
REPORTER'S MACHINE.
THAT WAS THE ONLY WAY
I COULD GET HIM TO STOP TYPING!
OH.
HI. HOW ARE THE GELLERS?
DON'T CALL US THAT.
THE JUDGE WOULDN'T LET
US GET AN ANNULMENT.
NOW WE GOT TO
GET A DIVORCE!
DID A PORSCHE
THROW UP ON YOU?
HEY, THAT'S PORSCH-AH!
LOOK AT ME TAKING CARE OF YOU
WITH NO PROBLEM, HUH?
YOU GUYS FEEL SAFE, RIGHT?
OKAY, I'M GOING TO TAKE THAT
SPIT-BUBBLE AS A "YEAH, I DO."
OKAY, LET'S GET RID OF THIS
DIRTY DIAPER, LESLIE.
I'LL SET YOU UP
WITH A NICE CLEAN ONE.
OKAY, I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO SCARE YOU.
I JUST HAVE TO CLEAN
THAT UP, OKAY?
'CAUSE, LET'S FACE IT,
WE'RE AT MONICA'S.
OKAY. I BROKE IT.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, THAT'S JUST
THE WAY THINGS GO.
OKAY. GOOD.
WHY ARE THERE ONLY TWO OF YOU?
WHERE'S LESLIE?
WELL, YOU CAN'T ANSWER.
LESLIE, WHERE ARE YOU, LESLIE?
LESLIE, NOW WOULD BE A GOOD
TIME FOR YOUR FIRST WORDS.
( murmurs )
WELL, LOOK AT YOU.
HEY...
YOU ARE A LITTLE BIT
MISCHIEVOUS.
MY GOSH.
OH, YOU'RE A LOT MISCHIEVOUS.
WELL, IT'LL DRY.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO PLAY.
YOU SIT WITH YOUR BROTHER
AND SISTER NOW
WHO AREN'T THERE.
HI.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
WELL, I SHOULD SAY THAT KROG
WILL BE FULLY EQUIPPED
TO DESTROY THE UNIVERSE AGAIN
IN 12 TO 14 HOURS.
OKAY.
SO, I TOTALLY TOOK
CARE OF THE BABIES
ALL BY MYSELF.
I FED THEM, BATHED THEM
AND PUT THEM TO BED.
AND PROTECTED THEM
FROM A TORNADO?
OH, MY GOD.
I KNOW.
THE BABIES ARE ASLEEP.
PHOEBE, WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
I DID IT.
I TOOK CARE OF THE BABIES
ALL BY MYSELF.
B-B-BUT MY APARTMENT?
WAS THE SETTING
OF PHOEBE'S TRIUMPH.
BUT THE MESS...
IS NOT AS IMPORTANT
AS THE FACT
THAT PHOEBE TOOK CARE
OF THE BABIES ALL BY HERSELF.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE RIGHT,
I SHOULDN'T FREAK OUT
'CAUSE THIS IS WHAT
IT'S GOING TO BE LIKE
WHEN YOU AND I HAVE BABIES.
WHEN WILL THAT BE?
WOULD YOU TAKE A
LOOK AT THIS MESS?
OH, HONEY,
THANK GOD YOU'RE HOME.
I WAS GETTING WORRIED.
I PICKED UP THE DIVORCE PAPERS.
UH, I'VE ALREADY
SIGNED EVERYTHING
AND I PUT LITTLE X's
WHERE YOU NEED TO SIGN.
OH, LITTLE X's... GREAT.
THAT MAKES UP
FOR EVERYTHING.
YOU KNOW, YOU'VE DONE A LOT
OF STUPID STUFF, TOO, OKAY?
OH, NAME ONE STUPID THING
THAT IS AS STUPID AS THIS ONE.
OKAY, HOW ABOUT YOU FLEW
TO LONDON TO STOP MY WEDDING.
UH, HOW ABOUT YOU TOLD ME
YOU LOVED ME
AFTER I WAS ALREADY MARRIED.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT WAS DIFFERENT.
I DID THOSE THINGS
BECAUSE I WAS IN LOVE WITH YOU.
YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT'S VERY DIFFERENT.
SO, LET'S...
LET'S JUST SIGN THE PAPERS.
WHAT?
NOTHING.
OKAY, CAN WE JUST
SIGN, PLEASE?
MM-HMM.
CONGRATULATIONS.
OKAY, WAIT, ROSS.
WAIT A MINUTE. UM...
I, UH...
KIND OF HAVE
A LITTLE CONFESSION.
WHAT?
UH, WELL, YOU KNOW THIS WHOLE
MARRIAGE THING...
KIND OF MY IDEA.
EXCUSE ME?
UH, WELL, REMEMBER
HOW WE WERE TOO DRUNK
TO REMEMBER ANYTHING
THE NIGHT WE WERE MARRIED?
YEAH.
AND, UH...
YEAH, I DIDN'T WANT
TO SAY ANYTHING
BUT IT JUST KEPT
COMING BACK TO ME
AND, UM, REMEMBER
WE WERE IN THE CASINO
AND FOR SOME REASON
YOU THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE FUNNY
TO EAT A LOT OF GRAPES?
AND, UH, AND I THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE FUNNIER
IF WE GOT MARRIED.
SO, AS A COMPROMISE,
WE DECIDED FIRST TO GET MARRIED
AND THEN...
Both:
TO EAT A LOT OF GRAPES.
SO, UM, SORRY I GOT US
INTO THIS WHOLE THING.
SO, THEN, I MEAN, IF
YOU THINK ABOUT IT
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT.
YEAH, DON'T PUSH IT THOUGH.
I GOT TO SAY, I KNOW I DIVORCE
A LOT OF WOMEN.
NEVER THOUGHT
I'D BE DIVORCING YOU.
I KNOW.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT
IF YOU AND I GOT MARRIED
THAT WOULD BE THE ONE
THAT STUCK.
AND IT WOULDN'T BE A SECRET.
AND WE WOULDN'T HAVE
OUR WEDDING DINNER AT PIZZA HUT.
OH... DID I...
DID I EVEN TREAT?
NO, IT WAS ON THE HOUSE.
IT WAS A NEWLYWED SPECIAL.
THAT MAY BE THE MOST DEPRESSING
THING I'VE HEARD IN MY LIFE.
YEAH.
I SHOULD PROBABLY GET THESE
TO MY LAWYER'S OFFICE.
YEAH-- HEY, THANKS, ROSS
FOR TAKING CARE
OF ALL THIS.
AH, NO PROBLEM.
I'M GOING TO NEED
A COPY OF THOSE.
TOTALLY.
YEAH.
HEY! HEY!
CAREFUL AROUND MY PORSCHE.
HI, JOEY.
HEY, HOW YOU DOING?
HE HAS THE MOST AMAZING
PORSCHE UNDER THERE.
I'D LOVE TO SHOW YOU,
BUT I JUST TUCKED HER IN.
SHE'S SLEEPING.
( giggles )
HEY, WOULD YOU TWO GIRLS
LIKE TO GO FOR A DRINK?
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]